const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"What is the cause of panacinar emphysema?","answers":[{"option":"Exposure to air pollutants","bool":false},{"option":"Past severe infection","bool":false},{"option":"Excessive smoking","bool":false},{"option":"Alpha-1 antitrypsin deficiency","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A patient is taking some kind of RNA synthesis inhibitor for the treatment of a mycobacterium infection. They return back to the clinic extremely worried about recent events. They claim their urine, saliva, sweat, tears, and feces are all reddish-orange in color. What drug is the patient most likely to be taking?","answers":[{"option":"Ethambutol","bool":false},{"option":"Streptomycin","bool":false},{"option":"Cycloserine","bool":false},{"option":"Rifampin","bool":true},{"option":"Isoniazide","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Smoking is associated with which of the following subtypes of emphysema?","answers":[{"option":"Centriacinar","bool":true},{"option":"Distal acinar","bool":false},{"option":"Paraseptal acinar","bool":false},{"option":"Septal acinar","bool":false},{"option":"Panacinar","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"What is the most common type of bronchogenic carcinoma?","answers":[{"option":"Small cell carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Adenocarcinoma","bool":true},{"option":"Squamous cell carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Large cell carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Bronchoalveolar carcinoma","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Atopic asthma most commonly manifests at what age?","answers":[{"option":"Old age","bool":false},{"option":"Childhood","bool":true},{"option":"Teenage","bool":false},{"option":"Neonatal","bool":false},{"option":"Adulthood","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Nuclear medicine comes under which of the following fields?","answers":[{"option":"Hematology","bool":false},{"option":"Urology","bool":false},{"option":"Radiology","bool":true},{"option":"Pediatrics","bool":false},{"option":"Otolaryngology","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which of the following refers to the study of man and machinery in a workplace?","answers":[{"option":"Bioscience","bool":false},{"option":"Ergonomics","bool":true},{"option":"Biotechnology","bool":false},{"option":"Environmental study","bool":false},{"option":"Community medicine","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 40-year-old female presents with exertional dyspnea, fatigue, and peripheral edema. Physical examination reveals an elevated jugular venous pressure and a loud pulmonary component of the second heart sound. An echocardiogram demonstrates dilated right ventricle. Which of the following is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Pulmonary artery aneurysm","bool":false},{"option":"Pulmonary embolism","bool":false},{"option":"Pulmonary edema","bool":false},{"option":"Pulmonary hypertension","bool":true},{"option":"Pulmonary vasculitis","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 72-year-old female presents with bilateral hilar lymphadenopathy on the chest x-ray. She has been experiencing fatigue, dry cough, and shortness of breath. Laboratory tests show an elevated serum angiotensin-converting enzyme (ACE) level. A biopsy of the affected lymph node reveals non-caseating granulomas. Which of the following is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Lung cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Tuberculosis","bool":false},{"option":"Hodgkin lymphoma","bool":false},{"option":"Sarcoidosis","bool":true},{"option":"Silicosis","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 65-year-old male presents with fever, productive cough, and pleuritic chest pain. Physical examination reveals decreased breath sounds and dullness to percussion over the right lower lung field. Chest x-ray shows hilar lymphadenopathy and right-sided pleural effusion. Thoracentesis is performed, and the fluid analysis reveals raised white blood cell count with lymphocytosis. Microscopy reveals acid-fast bacilli. Which of the following is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Parapneumonic effusion","bool":false},{"option":"Empyema","bool":false},{"option":"Chylothorax","bool":false},{"option":"Malignant pleural effusion","bool":false},{"option":"Tuberculous pleural effusion","bool":true}]},{"id":10,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which type of hypersensitivity reaction causes antigen-trigger degranulation of sensitized mast cell residents in the nasal or bronchiolar mucosae?","answers":[{"option":"Type IV","bool":false},{"option":"Type II","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Type III","bool":false},{"option":"Type I","bool":true}]},{"id":11,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which of the following interleukin cause the recruitment of eosinophils at the site of inflammation?","answers":[{"option":"Interleukin 5","bool":true},{"option":"Interleukin 1","bool":false},{"option":"Interleukin 4","bool":false},{"option":"Interleukin 2","bool":false},{"option":"Interleukin 3","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 64-year-old man with 35 pack-year smoking history presents with shortness of breath. On physical examination, he is a thin, cyanotic man in moderate respiratory distress. His chest shows an increased anterior posterior diameter and breath sounds are faint with prolonged expiration. Which parameter is most likely to be found on the pulmonary function test?","answers":[{"option":"Normal FEV1 and FVC ratio","bool":false},{"option":"Increased FEV1 and FVC ratio","bool":false},{"option":"Increased forced vital capacity","bool":false},{"option":"Decreased total lung capacity","bool":false},{"option":"Decreased FEV1 and FVC ratio","bool":true}]},{"id":13,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 65-year-old man comes to the office due to shortness of breath and peripheral edema. His symptoms have progressed in the last few months and have begun to limit his daily activity. The patient has 35 pack per year of smoking history. Physical examination reveals decreased breathing sounds. Chest x-ray reveals hyperinflated lungs. Which of the following is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Chronic pulmonary obstructive disease","bool":true},{"option":"Pulmonary hypertension","bool":false},{"option":"Lung abscess","bool":false},{"option":"Pulmonary embolism","bool":false},{"option":"Bronchiectasis","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"One morning, a dead body was reported in a bedroom. The body was  suspended with a running noose around its neck. Dribbling of saliva was observed from the corner of the mouth. What will be the findings in case of ante-mortem hanging?","answers":[{"option":"Post mortem lividity on both feet","bool":false},{"option":"Ligature around the neck","bool":false},{"option":"Ligature around the thyroid cartilage","bool":false},{"option":"Ligature not circling completely around the neck","bool":false},{"option":"Dribbling of saliva","bool":true}]},{"id":15,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A person died in an earthquake. A heavy piece of concrete was found over his chest. No other external injuries were present over his body. What type of asphyxia will you declare?","answers":[{"option":"Lynching","bool":false},{"option":"Traumatic","bool":true},{"option":"Autoerotic hanging","bool":false},{"option":"Garroting","bool":false},{"option":"Suffocation","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A dead body was found under a collapsed building. A heavy piece of concrete was found over the chest. No external injury was present over the body. What classic injury is feature of traumatic asphyxia?","answers":[{"option":"Fracture of upper limb","bool":false},{"option":"Head fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Spinal fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Flail chest","bool":true},{"option":"Fracture of lower limb","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"What is needed by the doctor before performing an autopsy?","answers":[{"option":"Police order","bool":true},{"option":"Presence of magistrate","bool":false},{"option":"Dead body chalan","bool":false},{"option":"Detailed history of illness","bool":false},{"option":"Permission from relatives","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"In pathological autopsy, the basic objective is to find which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Virus responsible for death","bool":false},{"option":"Manner of death","bool":false},{"option":"Pathophysiology of disease","bool":false},{"option":"Time of death","bool":false},{"option":"Cause of death","bool":true}]},{"id":19,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"In the death of a factory worker due to chronic metal poisoning which of the following should be preserved by the doctor?","answers":[{"option":"Any bone","bool":true},{"option":"Blood","bool":false},{"option":"Stomach and contents","bool":false},{"option":"Liver piece","bool":false},{"option":"Brain tissue","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which general preservative is used in a mortuary?","answers":[{"option":"Formalin","bool":false},{"option":"Saturated saline solution","bool":false},{"option":"Formaldehyde","bool":true},{"option":"Spirit","bool":false},{"option":"Absolute alcohol","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A dead body arrives at the mortuary. The death is because of radiation in some laboratories. During postmortem what precaution would you not adopt?","answers":[{"option":"Don't perform autopsy if you have any cuts in hands","bool":false},{"option":"Used long handled instruments","bool":false},{"option":"Perform autopsy in open atmosphere","bool":true},{"option":"Freeze body for 12 hours prior to autopsy","bool":false},{"option":"Use proper doubled gloves","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 4-year-old child is brought to the emergency room with complaints of cough for 2 days and shortness of breath since evening. He had similar complaints in the past also. Father has a history of atopic allergy. On examination, his respiratory rate is 54/min, and on auscultation, bilateral wheeze is present. What is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Tracheitis","bool":false},{"option":"Asthma","bool":true},{"option":"Pneumonia","bool":false},{"option":"Bronchiolitis","bool":false},{"option":"Croup","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which of the following drugs used for the treatment of tuberculosis is bacteriostatic?","answers":[{"option":"Ethambutol","bool":true},{"option":"Streptomycin","bool":false},{"option":"Pyrazinamide","bool":false},{"option":"Isoniazid","bool":false},{"option":"Rifampin","bool":false}]},{"id":24,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which of the following drugs used in first-line tuberculosis have a narrow spectrum?","answers":[{"option":"Capreomycin","bool":false},{"option":"Gatifloxacin","bool":false},{"option":"Rifabutin","bool":false},{"option":"Isoniazid","bool":true},{"option":"Ethionamide","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"In the short course regimen of treatment of tuberculosis of 6 months, how many months are pyrazinamide and ethambutol used for?","answers":[{"option":"Throughout the course","bool":false},{"option":"Initial two months","bool":true},{"option":"Initial three months","bool":false},{"option":"Initial one month","bool":false},{"option":"Lat 2 months","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"According to the World Health Organization guidelines, new (untreated) sputum smear-positive cases of pulmonary tuberculosis should be treated with which of the following regimen?","answers":[{"option":"Isoniazid, ethambutol, rifampin, and pyrazinamide for 6 months along with pyridoxine","bool":false},{"option":"Isoniazid and rifampin for 6 months with additional pyrazinamide in the initial two months","bool":false},{"option":"Isoniazid, thioacetazone, and rifampin for 2 months followed by isoniazid and thioacetazone for 6 months","bool":false},{"option":"Isoniazid, rifampin, and pyrazinamide for 6 months","bool":false},{"option":"Isoniazid and rifampin for 6 months with additional pyrazinamide and ethambutol during the initial two months","bool":true}]},{"id":27,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which of the following anti-asthmatic drug produces rapid and long-acting bronchodilation?","answers":[{"option":"Salmeterol","bool":true},{"option":"Metaproterenol","bool":false},{"option":"Bitolterol","bool":false},{"option":"Albuterol","bool":false},{"option":"Prednisolone","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"An air pollutant that produces as a result of incomplete combustion of fossil fuels or any other organic matter, and when inhaled, it mimics oxygen. It can bind to the hemoglobin in the blood and prevent it from carrying oxygen. Which air pollutant is this statement referring to?","answers":[{"option":"Ozone","bool":false},{"option":"Carbon dioxide","bool":false},{"option":"Carbon monoxide","bool":true},{"option":"Nitrogen oxide","bool":false},{"option":"Sulfur dioxide","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Acid rain refers to highly acidic precipitation. The normal pH of rain is slightly acidic (~5.6), due to the reaction of carbon dioxide with rainwater. The pH of acid rain drops below 5.6. It becomes 4.4-4.2. Which oxides contribute to acid rain?","answers":[{"option":"Nitrogen and hydrocarbons","bool":false},{"option":"Sulphur and hydrocarbons","bool":false},{"option":"Nitrogen and carbon dioxide","bool":false},{"option":"Sulphur and nitrogen","bool":true},{"option":"Sulphur and carbon dioxide","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which of the following is the most appropriate asthma diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Strong family history of asthma and raised serum IgE","bool":false},{"option":"Post bronchodilator FEV1/FVC less than 70% on spirometry","bool":false},{"option":"Chest X-ray shows hyperinflation","bool":false},{"option":"Wheezing on chest auscultation","bool":false},{"option":"Increase in FEV1 of 12% and 200ml after bronchodilators in an obstructive pattern on spirometry","bool":true}]},{"id":31,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"In a patient suspected of community-acquired pneumonia who has mild symptoms. Which of the following tests is/are indicated?","answers":[{"option":"Sputum for culture and sensitivity (C/S)","bool":false},{"option":"Complete blood count (CBC)","bool":false},{"option":"CBC, X-ray, chest PA view, sputum C/S","bool":false},{"option":"None","bool":true},{"option":"Blood culture (C/S)","bool":false}]},{"id":32,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A patient diagnosed with pulmonary tuberculosis has never taken antitubercular drugs before. Which of the following regimens is most appropriate?","answers":[{"option":"3 months of isoniazid, rifampicin, pyrazinamide, and ethambutol followed by 5 months of isoniazid, rifampicin, and ethambutol","bool":false},{"option":"2 months of isoniazid, rifampicin, pyrazinamide, and ethambutol followed by 4 months of isoniazid and rifampicin","bool":true},{"option":"6 months of isoniazid, rifampicin, pyrazinamide, and ethambutol","bool":false},{"option":"2 months of isoniazid and rifampicin followed by 2 months of pyrazinamide and ethambutol","bool":false},{"option":"2 months of isoniazid, rifampicin, pyrazinamide, and ethambutol followed by 2 months of isoniazid and rifampicin","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 70-year-old male known smoker presents to the emergency room with complaints of fever and cough for 4 days and shortness of breath for 1 day. On examination, he is in respiratory distress with a blood pressure of 90/60, pulse of 110/min, temperature of 101F, and respiratory rate of 36/min. His chest x-ray shows consolidation on the right lower lobe with effusion. His calculated CURB-65 score is 4. Which of the following is the most appropriate step of management?","answers":[{"option":"Treat as ventilator associated pneumonia with MRSA coverage","bool":false},{"option":"Treat outpatient with oral antibiotics","bool":false},{"option":"Treat as hospital acquired pneumonia with injectable antibiotics","bool":false},{"option":"Treat in HDU/ICU as severe pneumonia","bool":true},{"option":"Treat inpatient in ward with oral antibiotics","bool":false}]},{"id":34,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 32-year-old male who has a history of asthma comes to the emergency department with complaints of severe shortness of breath and productive cough for the last 1 week. Arterial blood gases (ABGs) are done showing pH 7.35, PO2=60 mm of Hg, PCO2=25mm of Hg, and HCO3=20. What will be the best interpretation of his arterial blood gases  (ABGs) report?","answers":[{"option":"Type II respiratory failure","bool":false},{"option":"Type I respiratory failure","bool":true},{"option":"Respiratory alkalosis","bool":false},{"option":"Respiratory failure","bool":false},{"option":"Respiratory acidosis","bool":false}]},{"id":35,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 50-year-old male chain smoker for the past 20 years presents to the emergency room with progressive shortness of breath, fever, and productive cough for 5 days. On examination, bilateral rhonchi are present. Arterial blood gas (ABGs) report shows a pH of 7.38, PO2=54 mm of Hg, PCO2=55 mm of Hg, and HCO3=26 mEq/L. What is the likely interpretation of his ABGs?","answers":[{"option":"Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease","bool":false},{"option":"Metabolic acidosis","bool":false},{"option":"Metabolic alkalosis","bool":false},{"option":"Type I respiratory failure","bool":false},{"option":"Type II respiratory failure","bool":true}]},{"id":36,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 63-year-old male patient with a history of diabetes and chronic obstructive lung disease presents to the emergency department with fever, productive cough, and shortness of breath for the past 3 days. On examination, he appears acutely ill with crackles on lung auscultation. A chest x-ray reveals a lobar consolidation in the right upper lobe. Sputum culture grows staphylococcus aureus. What will the gram stain show?","answers":[{"option":"Gram negative cocci","bool":false},{"option":"Gram positive diplococci","bool":false},{"option":"Gram positive cocci in cluster","bool":true},{"option":"Gram negative cocci in chain","bool":false},{"option":"Gram positive bacilli","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 50-year male presents to the emergency department with high-grade fever, severe headache, myalgias, and non-productive cough. He recently returned from a vacation where he visited a popular hotel with an outdoor pool. On examination, his temperature is 40°C (104°F), and lung auscultation reveals scattered crackles. Laboratory test shows hyponatremia and elevated liver function tests. A chest x-ray demonstrates patchy infiltrates in bilateral lower lobes. Gram stains reveal gram-negative rods. Which organism is most likely involved?","answers":[{"option":"Yersinia pestis","bool":false},{"option":"Escherichia col","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudomonas aeruginosa","bool":false},{"option":"Legionella pneumophila","bool":true},{"option":"Neisseria meningitidis","bool":false}]},{"id":38,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 72-year-old male with a history of chronic liver failure, diabetes mellitus, and hypertension is admitted to the intensive care unit (ICU) for septic shock secondary to a urinary tract infection. He is intubated upon admission and started on broad-spectrum antibiotics. On the third day of hospitalization, the patient develops a fever of 104.2°F (39.1°C) and increased purulent secretions. Chest x-ray reveals new infiltrates in the right upper lobe. Gram stain of sputum reveals gram-negative rods. Which of the following organism is the most likely cause of this patient's hospital-acquired pneumonia?","answers":[{"option":"Moraxella catarrhalis","bool":false},{"option":"Mycoplasma pneumoniae","bool":false},{"option":"Neisseria meningitidis","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudomonas aeruginosa","bool":true},{"option":"Candida albicans","bool":false}]},{"id":39,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 4-year-old child presents with a history of low-grade fever and cough for the past 2 days. The cough is characteristically barking with hoarseness of voice. On examination, there is inspiratory stridor with no drooling or respiratory distress. What is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Tonsillitis","bool":false},{"option":"Pertussis","bool":false},{"option":"Epiglottitis","bool":false},{"option":"Pharyngitis","bool":false},{"option":"Croup","bool":true}]},{"id":40,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 3-year-old healthy child suddenly develops a sore throat and fever. Within hours, the patient appears toxic, swallowing with difficulty and drooling, and labored breathing. The neck is hyperextended, and the child assumes the tripod position. What is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Acute epiglottitis","bool":true},{"option":"Diphtheria","bool":false},{"option":"Croup","bool":false},{"option":"Asthma","bool":false},{"option":"Bronchiolitis","bool":false}]},{"id":41,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A woman aged 25 has been diagnosed with pulmonary tuberculosis. She is also 8 months pregnant. When should she start her antitubercular therapy?","answers":[{"option":"Delayed till after confinement","bool":false},{"option":"Delayed till the end of first trimester","bool":false},{"option":"Start immediately","bool":true},{"option":"Delayed till the end of third trimester","bool":false},{"option":"Delayed till the end of second trimester","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 50-year-old male presents to the outpatient department with complaints of fever and cough for the last 5 days. On examination, his blood pressure is 120/90, pulse is 100/min, the temperature is 101F, respiratory rate is 30/min. Chest examination reveals bronchial breathing with dull percussion notes on the right lower lobes with increased vocal resonance. Which of the following investigation would confirm the diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Complete blood count","bool":false},{"option":"CT chest","bool":false},{"option":"Arterial blood gases","bool":false},{"option":"Sputum culture","bool":false},{"option":"Chest X-ray (PA view)","bool":true}]},{"id":43,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 55-year-old female without known comorbidities presents to the outpatient department with complaints of fever and cough for 1 week. On examination, her blood pressure is 100/70, her pulse is 90/min, her respiratory rate is 20/min, and her temperature is 100F. On chest examination, her bronchial breathing in the left lower zone with decreased breath sound and increased vocal resonance. Her chest x-ray shows consolidation in the left lower lung. Which organism is responsible for her current illness?","answers":[{"option":"Mycobacterium tuberculosis","bool":false},{"option":"Staphylococcus aureus","bool":false},{"option":"Legionella pneumophila","bool":false},{"option":"Streptococcus pneumoniae","bool":true},{"option":"Chlamydia pneumoniae","bool":false}]},{"id":44,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 66-year-old man with 35 pack per year smoking history presents with shortness of breath. On physical examination, he is a thin, cyanotic man in moderate pulmonary distress. His chest shows an increased anterior-posterior diameter. Pulmonary function test reveals a markedly decreased FEV1 to FVC ratio. If a lung biopsy is performed on this patient, then which of the following features are most likely present on the microscope?","answers":[{"option":"Septic infarcts","bool":false},{"option":"Granulomatous inflammation","bool":false},{"option":"Curschmann spirals","bool":false},{"option":"Charcot Leyden crystals","bool":false},{"option":"Abnormally large alveoli are separated by thin septa with centriacinar fibrosis","bool":true}]},{"id":45,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"Which of the following statement is correct regarding terbutaline?","answers":[{"option":"Inhibiting the guanylyl cyclase","bool":false},{"option":"Produces skeletal muscle relaxation","bool":false},{"option":"Prolonged administration leads to down-regulation of receptors","bool":true},{"option":"Can be administered trans-dermal","bool":false},{"option":"Metabolized by COMT","bool":false}]},{"id":46,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 45-year-old male presents with a 2-week history of fever, cough, and pleuritic chest pain. Physical examination reveals decreased breath sounds over the right lower lung field. Chest X-ray shows a moderate-sized right-sided pleural effusion. Thoracentesis is performed, and the fluid is sent for analysis. Microscopic examination reveals numerous neutrophils, fibrin strands, and gram-positive cocci in a chain. Which of the following is the most likely diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Tuberculosis","bool":false},{"option":"Empyema","bool":true},{"option":"Pulmonary embolism","bool":false},{"option":"Lung adenocarcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Mesothelioma","bool":false}]},{"id":47,"info":"3rd-year/respiratory/2023","question":"A 6-month-old infant is brought to the emergency department with symptoms of respiratory distress. The child has had a runny nose and cough for the past few days, which has worsened. On examination, the infant has tachypnea, wheezing, and subcostal retractions. Chest x-ray shows hyperinflation and peri-bronchial thickening. Which of the following is the most likely etiologic agent?","answers":[{"option":"Rhinovirus","bool":false},{"option":"Respiratory syncytial virus","bool":true},{"option":"Influenza virus","bool":false},{"option":"Adenovirus","bool":false},{"option":"Para-influenza virus type 3","bool":false}]}]
export default arr